I can't thank you enough, Noor.
I should thank you!
I appreciate you always calling on me,
Auntie Stella.
Hup!
I'll see you again soon, Noor!
Nice work today.
Noor!
Thanks to you, we'll have no problem
sticking to the construction schedule.
Oh yeah? Glad to hear it.
What's that?
Someone... please, help me!
Hey, Noor!
That's a huge... cow!
Northwest Clays Kingdom (15 Years Ago)
Here, Mom.
It might be hot, so be careful.
It's perfect. Thank you.
Time to feed the goats.
I have to bring them to the hill.
Noor.
I know.
I won't go beyond the rock. I promise.
I'll get a wild rabbit
and some nuts and seeds later.
We'll have soup.
Give me a sec. I'll boil some more water.
Noor...
Yes?
I'm so sorry I'm unable
to do anything for you.
But at least live the life you want to.
Soup's ready!
Mom.
Mom?
Mom!
Noor, it's time for bed.
What's tonight's story?
It's about an adventurer.
What's an adventurer?
Well...
Someone who once, with their friends,
slayed a gigantic dragon,
and learned magic spells
from an old sorceror,
broke a curse cast upon a forest,
and obtained a cure-all elixir
from the king of the dead.
No matter the predicament,
they will raise their swords and
strike down evil for the sake of their friends.
That is an adventurer.
I wanna hear it! I wanna hear it!
All right, now which shall I start with?
An adventurer...
But at least live the life you want to.
Don't eat it all at once!
Dad, Mom...
I'm leaving town for the first time ever.
I'm going to be an adventurer.
Goodbye for now.
Just off the main road...
Thank you.
This is the place!
This place ain't for kids. Get outta here.
The guards at the gate said
I could be an adventurer if I came here.
Don't be stupid.
You're gonna worry your parents.
They're dead. Both of them.
No parents, huh...
Can't do nothin' about that.
What's your name?
Noor.
"Noor," huh?
Headin' to the training school
for different classes, then?
Never had a kid like you
do this before, but...
Do what?
Now listen good.
Hopefuls wantin' to register with the
royal capital's Adventurer's Guild
go to lessons at the royal training school.
Basically, you'll get training
for your job class.
If you wanna be an adventurer,
go acquire some skills first.
Skills?
The art of the sword or magic,
stuff like that.
I'm going right now!
A swordsman...
Heroes in the storybooks
can fell a dragon
as big as a mountain in a single swing!
I did it!
A Few Months Later
That's enough, Noor.
Unfortunately...
Wait! Just give me a little longer-
There's no point.
Going any further is a waste of your time.
The only thing you've retained
is parrying to evade an attack...
Perhaps it would be better
if you chose another path.
Your talent may be found
in another training school.
Warrior...
While fighting with any weapon imaginable,
you risk your life and
become a shield for your allies!
That's pretty close to an adventurer!
I acknowledge your efforts,
A Few Months Later
but what you've acquired
is a slight improvement of your physical abilities.
If you force yourself to continue on,
you will lose your life.
A hunter!
You totally lack the sense to
handle any sort of delicate weaponry!
A thief!
You could not dismantle the trap
on the treasure chest,
and you can't sense anyone's presence
so you becoming a spy
is out of the question.
Magician!
To think you've come this far
yet all you can manage is Tiny Flame.
It's rare to see people
as incapable of magic as you are!
A cleric...
Though you can heal light scratches,
it's impressive that you do use low-level healing
without being naturally blessed.
You didn't get one decent skill?!
You spent a full three-month term
practicing at every training school,
and you couldn't get a single one?
Noor...
Sorry, but I can't let you register
as an adventurer like that.
I'm no prodigy.
I'm back, Dad, Mom.
I truly have no talent for anything.
I know that for sure now.
In that case...
I must take what I can
and train much, much harder!
My swordsman instructor told me...
If you practice one skill repeatedly,
you may be able to master a new skill.
Parry!
This is my skill that I acquired
at the swordsman class training.
I will train!
Morning... noon... and night!
1 Year Later
I can evade ten swords in one breath now.
I don't have any new skills yet,
but I am getting better.
3 Years Later
A hundred swords in one breath...
But I still haven't acquired any new skills.
At this rate, becoming an adventurer
is nothing but a pipe dream.
I have to try harder.
I must train more intensely!
10 Years Later
These past 14 years,
I've trained every day without fail and
I can now parry a thousand wooden swords.
And yet, no new skills...
All right, one last try.
Parry, Physical Enhancement, Stone Throw,
Featherstep, Tiny Flame, Low Heal...
Um... Are you sure this is what you have?
That's all of it.
W-well then, are you aware of the royal capital's
class training school system?
Here in the capital, you can take lessons
from any of our distinguished instructors and-
I know.
I've already been through all of them.
Every one of them?!
If that's the case...
I really can't register, can I?
I am truly sorry.
No, you don't need to apologize.
There's really nothing I can do, huh?
Hey, you, mind not picking
on my new hire, huh?
Master!
It's been awhile, sir!
What? I have no idea who you are...
Oh, wait a second...
Is that... you, Noor?!
So you kept up with your own
solo training this whole time, huh?
Are you okay with that?
So you kept up with your own
solo training this whole time, huh?
Yes.
But in the end, I've only been able
to improve my parrying skill a little.
Listen up, Noor.
There are different ranks of adventurers.
S-rank being the highest,
and E-rank the lowest.
To be recognized as an E-rank,
you gotta have more than one useful skill.
But, you don't have that.
I can't do anything but give up now, huh?
However, that doesn't mean there's
no other way for you to be an adventurer.
Are you sure?!
There's actually
something lower than E-rank.
What?
The outlying F-rank, which is basically
unheard of even to the people involved.
Then can I register for that one?!
But there are conditions to it.
You're forbidden from taking any quests
that involve killing anything
or venturing out of the city to gather items.
What you can accept are miscellaneous tasks
around the city, and that's about it.
No one's dumb enough to go to the trouble
of becoming an adventurer
just to do those requests, right?
And I'd end up with the job placement fee.
Well, it used to be a job
for beggars 'round the city, so-
I'm okay with that.
Well, it used to be a job
for beggars 'round the city, so-
Did you hear what I said?
I don't mind. Register me for that.
Here's your F-rank adventurer license.
Thank you!
I owe you everything, sir!
Physical Enhancement.
Featherstep.
Thank goodness!
Low Heal.
Tiny Flame.
Stone Throw!
My dream of becoming an adventurer
and being of use to people has come true.
Anything beyond this...
may be asking for too much.
I'll see you again soon, Noor!
Nice work today.
Noor!
Thanks to you, we'll have no problem
sticking to the construction schedule.
Oh yeah? Glad to hear it.
What's that?
Someone... please, help me!
Hey, Noor!
That's a huge... cow?!
I've only seen these things in books,
but is the actual thing really this big?!
Surround it and block it's movements!
We have to protect her!
Do something to distract it!
Are you all right?!
He's dead.
They're gonna get killed!
Stone Throw!
I gotta do it now!
It's fast!
Parry!
So much force!
One blow from that and I'm dead!
I need an opening to counterattack!
No, even if there was one...
I have no attack skills!
The girl!
She's still here?!
Featherstep!
Even if...
Even if I can't become
the adventurer hero...
I want to at least be able to protect
the frightened girl in front of me!
No matter the predicament,
they will raise their swords and
strike down evil for the weak,
and for the sake of their friends.
That is an adventurer!
Parry!
That was a close one...
I would have absolutely been slaughtered
by anything bigger.
And I thought I could travel the world
and go on adventures at this level...
E-excuse me...
Thank you so much.
I'm alive because of you.
Oh, that's great.
Too bad about them, though.
If it's okay, may I have your name?
Well, I'm not anyone important.
Please, wai-
Lady Lynneburg!
You're safe!
Y-yes, I'm...
I can't believe that one loose cow in the city
that isn't even a demon was such a menace.
I still have more training to do.
#1: I Parry a Cow